{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2110","name":"Hangover's Lounge","address":"20143 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221","owner":"Tameka Watkins","licenseNumber":"202881","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.14217,42.44199","geojson":{"id":"2110","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.142165623,42.4419867410001]},"properties":{"name":"Hangover's Lounge","owner":"Tameka Watkins","address":"20143 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"202881","establishmentid":"2110","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/30/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5190","name":"D and D Cuisine LLC","address":"17521 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4245","name":"New Prospect Missionary Baptist Church","address":"6330 Pembroke St","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"51622720","name":"Durdens Catering LLC","address":"20504 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4356","name":"We Will Cook For You","address":"20504 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4266","name":"Baker's Keyboard Lounge","address":"20510 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1798","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #0820","address":"6333 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1243","name":"Pasteur Elementary School","address":"19811 Stoepel St","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1469","name":"Noni's Sherwood Grille","address":"19700 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"51622487","name":"Bucharest Grill","address":"19492 Livernois","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"3928","name":"1917 American Bistro","address":"19416 Livernois","zipcode":"48221"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45543","inspectionDate":"2019-03-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43563","inspectionDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"A designated dressing room/area shall be provided and used."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make easily accessible."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"8-303.10","violationDescription":"For FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS that are required to submit plans as specified under ยง 8-201.11 the REGULATORY AUTHORITY shall issue a PERMIT to the applicant after:\r\n(A) A properly completed application is submitted;\r\n(B) The required fee is submitted;\r\n(C) The required plans, specifications, and information are reviewed and APPROVED; and\r\n(D) A preoperational inspection as specified in ยง 8-203.10 shows that the establishment is built or remodeled in accordance with the APPROVED plans and specifications and that the establishment is in compliance with this Code.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"40960","inspectionDate":"2017-12-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make easily accessible."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"38626","inspectionDate":"2017-05-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-05-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2110"}}